Why are you following me?
Tell me now!
- No...
- No? You deny it?
So you haven't been following me
for a month and thirteen days?
- No...
- You still deny it?
- I mean...
- Go on, talk!
I'll stop following you.
Did I tell you to stop
following me? Did I?
- No.
- So?
Clear off!
What the hell's going on?
No.
You reject me.
You refuse to sleep with me.
And ever since
you've been following me.
What's going on your
stupid bloody mind?
- See?
- What? Your hands?
You're not just any girl.
How do I put it? You're special.
Must I explain?
If I must explain
how special I am,
what's your role then?
Role?
Whatever!
"Love these days"
The wise Internet knows
Who Kabir and Rumi are
The tips on love for every week day
Fill my head
You think you know it all
But when your time comes
Your body trembles
Life turns upside down
There's a pounding in your chest
Yes, it's our hearts beating fast
The knocking, the locking
The talking, the chatting
Our racing hearts
Till the end of the world
I have to live among heartbeats
Some say love is taking
Others say love is giving
Love has a million definitions
Though it cannot be defined
Might be artificial
or original
The problem is eternal
A day will come
when you can't escape
your beguiling heart
Our racing hearts
One sec.
- This isn't right.
- What?
We're under-utilizing
the situation.
What are you talking about?
Can you feel it?
- If you think I'm insulting you...
- Stay away from me.
No.
Just remember you've
got it wrong. OK?
Can I have your number?
F*** you!
A*****e!
Weird, just weird.
It didn't get there.
I can see him.
He's sipping a soda alone.
Who drinks a soda on their own?
No, he doesn't like me.
He's just weird.
Just be careful, babe,
in case he pops up again.
Hello.
Hi.
- You?
- Yes, me.
Co-working space?
- Do you rent space?
- Is that a problem?
- Sorry?
- You're renting?
It's damn important.
I'm a software programmer.
Don't I need a place to work?
I work all day long. Non-stop.
Where?
- Anywhere. Sit there.
- No, over here.
What's going on?
The moment you feel
I'm in your way,
I'll go.
Let me see you try.
Yeah! Correct.
Will you step outside?
Meet me outside the cafe.
What the hell's going on?
You reject me.
You refuse to sleep with me.
And ever since you've been
following me.
What's going on
in your stupid bloody mind?
How do I put it? You're special.
Must I explain?
If I must explain how special I am,
what's your role?
Whatever!
Hey, hero! All good?
OK then.
Where are you going?
- How are you going?
- By cab.
Why do you guys always go
the wrong way, driver?
Can you see my location?
Go on, tell me.
Hello!
Bye. OK?
- Where are you going?
- Anywhere.
The cab's taking forever.
Evening traffic. A bike is best.
No option.
- I'm going to Champa Gali.
- Me, too.
- Oh, come on.
- OK. Come.
- I don't need you for sex.
- What?
I can have sex with any girl.
You're something else!
See...
Maybe you're the one?
Who knows!
I'm here on a date.
- So?
- So nothing.
Just informing you. Thanks.
- That won't do.
- What?
You cannot thank me.
Whatever.
You're getting over-charged.
You do it to me, baby.
There's something about you.
No, there's something
about you.
You do this to yourself.
Not so close!
Another round?
So what do you think?
- I'm like this with all the girls?
- Aren't you?
I don't bring just anyone
to an expensive joint like this.
You're special, you know?
Know how much
a tequila costs here?
Where you going?
Take it back. I haven't touched it.
Wait!
Zoe!
Zoe, that was a better joint.
No. Here.
Come on. We'll have fun.
What's going on
in your stupid bloody mind?
What's your role?
And ever since
you've been following me.
He can't be far.
Is that your bike?
Are you blind?
Can't you see my car?
Can't you hear?
His ears are blocked.
Easy.
Hit the lowlife.
Let him go! He's a kid.
You'll kill him. Stop!
He hit me first.
Leave him alone.
Hello.
Barman.
Yes, ma'am?
What can I do for you?
Sorry. Yes, ma'am.
Give me something for
a headache.
Allow me!
- My special drink.
- What's that?
Long years of drinking experience.
Hope it works.
I have a very important meeting.
- So, how was your date?
- Excuse me?
The bike guy?
Costume change, blue mascara...
You went with the guy
who came here for you, right?
First of all,
it's none of your business.
And second of all...
- "Secondly."
- What?
"Second of all" is wrong.
It's "secondly."
Whatever.
I wasn't on a date with him.
He gave me a lift so I could
meet my date on time.
The poor sucker!
You should've dated
the biker instead. He's cool.
He's OK.
He's serious about you.
That's just the problem.
Too serious.
That's a problem?
Leena, I'm very serious about you.
He's serious about you
and that's a problem?
Of course.
I'm serious about you.
No matter what people tell you.
Excuse me. Please explain
the problem to me.
Being serious is a good thing
from where I come.
And where's that?
The old India. Many years ago.
Many years later - in new India,
there's this 22-year-old girl.
Who...
How do you say 1½
in Hindi?
- "Dedh."
- She hasn't even had "dedh" boyfriends.
So, of course she isn't serious
about a relationship.
Time for fun and exploration!
I'm putting all my energy
on my career.
Then, five years from now
when my event management company
is doing well and I earn good money
then it's serious relationship time.
- You think it'll all go to plan?
- Yes.
Time has passed.
Everything's changed.
This time will pass too.
And things will change again.
So what's new?
I'll tell you what's new --
this idiot.
He's new because he hasn't
changed one bit.
- Who?
- Him, who else?
You know he's just like me.
No, no, sorry.
He's not like me.
I was like him...
once upon a time.
"Kulfi for sale!"
This crazy heart of mine
Without my lover
Knows no peace
- Hurry up, brother!
- Raghu!
This crazy heart of mine
Never listens to reason
And there was this girl,
just like me?
She was not at all like you.
Leena.
- You have her photo on your phone?
- No mobiles in that era.
How did you manage
without mobiles?
We did. It didn't make
a difference.
This communication boom.
You say everything except
what you want to say.
That was left unspoken.
Wow!
Tell me what you could not say.
Oh, you got that?
So come on then.
Cut to flashback.
- How's my cravat?
- Solid!
- Hey, Raghu.
- Is that her?
Luck's on your side today.
Attention, boys and girls!
This is the evening
you all were waiting for
the Annual Socials.
One boy will go across to a girl
and request her for dance.
Who's going to start? Come on!
Don't be nervous!
Who is brave boy?
- Go on, Raghu!
- This is your chance.
Go, Raghu!
Don't back down, Raghu.
- Keep going!
- Go, Raghu. Go.
- Hello.
- Yes?
Would you like to breakdance?
Dance?
Well done!
Perhaps I'll never speak
the unspoken
Perhaps you'll understand anyway
Perhaps I'll find you in my dreams
Perhaps we'll find a meeting ground
Without you
There is no me
I want nothing more than you
Nothing less than you
Without you
I am not myself
I want nothing more than you
Nothing less than you
- What happened?
- No. Nothing.
You were OK yesterday.
- Did you have an accident?
- It's nothing.
Show me.
What?
I fill my eyes with dreams
Asking myself questions
Answering them myself
On your behalf
I pretend to run errands
But wherever I go
I make sure to pass your street
I'll never stop trying
I want nothing more than you
Nothing less than you
Without you
There is no me
I want nothing more than you
Nothing less than you
Careful, you'll fall.
I can't take it anymore.
I can't hold back.
- Today's the day.
- For what?
What do you mean?
What can't you hold back?
Cheating.
This is cheating.
I don't have those sweet feelings.
Like the romantic song words
in the "QSQT" movie.
Those songs mislead you.
I'm not happy.
Where's the happiness?
At night I feel someone's
strangling me.
It's like I have a fever.
I can't breathe.
Someone is strangling me.
Like this!
No, Raghu, no!
That's it. I'm telling her.
Interview!
S***! S***!
Kill it, sexy!
Driver, I'm in a big hurry.
Tell me. Can you see my location?
Where did you turn?
Hello!
- You spooking me?
- No.
Wherever I go,
you're heading there.
- The moment you think...
- Yeah! Cyber Hub.
- I was going there...
- Shut up, let's go.
Having difficulty breathing?
Feels like someone's strangling
you at night?
No.
You mean you're sleeping well?
No. Yes.
When I hit the bed, I fall straight
to sleep.
Exactly an hour later,
I'm wide awake.
Then I can't get back to sleep till dawn.
Same story every night.
OK.
Next time you can't sleep,
you can SMS me.
About time.
Come.
Zoe Chauhan.
Boardroom number 3.
Good afternoon!
Zoe Chauhan. Hello.
Please have a seat.
Let me start by saying that
it'll be a rare honor for me
to work with such a hugely respected
and successful company
- as the Mehta Group of industries.
- No need for flattery.
And you can't be flattered.
You haven't organized
a single corporate event.
Who called you?
- Sir, HR.
- They have a shortlist...
Sir, I know I haven't organized
a corporate event before.
- Please look at our plans...
- Plans!
You have plans too?
I have it all planned till
I retire at 55.
All the milestones
are clearly marked, sir.
Before you entered the room,
you unbuttoned your blouse.
That part of the plan?
CCTV.
"Rock the interview! Veer."
Well?
Yes.
I did unbutton my top. I wanted
to make a good impression.
Is that how you make
a good impression?
By flaunting your body?
I couldn't leave my body at home
and come here.
In fact, I have to take it
everywhere I go.
So I do my best to make
myself attractive.
When I look attractive,
I feel confident.
And my work improves.
So I unbuttoned my top for myself,
not for anyone else.
Must everyone shut their eyes then?
- They can see you too.
- Let them.
It doesn't bother me.
If the others have a problem
it's because they have outdated ideas
and double standards. Really!
It's their problem.
Let them sort it out.
I don't know what
comes over me. God!
It's OK.
This bit*** inside of me,
will I ever control it?
No. Why control it?
You should let it out!
Because that's what you are.
That's the real you.
B***, blue whale, zebra.
Discover what you really are.
Who cares about the job!
Who cares? Hello!
If I didn't care, would I have spent
months slaving on this pitch?
It's the Mehta Group.
You have to do what feels right
from the inside.
From the inner you.
Every journey eventually
leads to your inner self.
- Who tells you these things?
- Kabir.
Guru Nanak, Rumi. Don't you
get forwards on your phone?
Wise words are everywhere. On pens,
books, stationery, truck stickers.
Mind-blowing wisdom.
Life-changing!
A new bar just opened near me.
Their coasters have wise quotes
on them...
You and I aren't happening.
If you like me,
then you'd better stop liking me.
To hell with my inner self!
I don't give a s***
about Life's Truths.
I wanna get my career going.
I'll make it solid so I'll never need
to depend on any guy.
I don't want to regret not having
done what I wanted in life.
OK. That's all good. Cool.
And what do you want to do
with your life?
- You taking the p***?
- What?
Making fun?
I should keep my mouth shut.
When you go for an interview
do you spout wise quotes
off truck stickers?
Yeah.
But this app is India-centric.
India-centric?
Won't Indian farmers use the app
to import foreign technology?
He's at a job interview.
He's picking holes in the job.
Like, hello?
Won't it reduce manpower?
This technology means 5 workers
take the place of a 100.
Where will the other 95 go?
He's been scouted three times
by US firms.
He gives them some stupid reason
and says no. Who the hell is he?
What is India's population?
It's very high.
Manpower is not our problem.
Insufficient labor is the West's problem.
Which we'll be importing
by using this app.
And you want me to make the app
India-centric?
And the best part is he thinks
he's doing the right thing.
I wish I was like him.
Huh?
- Whatever.
- It's intoxicating.
He risks losing out.
But he wants to follow his heart
and take a leap of faith.
That power, I had it once.
It's gone now.
I lost it.
You know thank God you lost it.
That's why you own this business.
I wish he'd lose that "power" too.
And get in line.
How long will he stay this stupid?
Lifelong, I hope.
And I wish
all this would vanish.
And I could be stupid again.
Come!
He's here.
Go ahead.
What is this place?
Never been here before.
I come here often.
Alone.
I mean it's the first time
I've come here.
- Go on.
- Huh?
- Raja said you wanted to talk to me.
- Yes.
What is it?
- I don't want to kiss you.
- What?
That's not the main reason.
What's happening to me?
Is that how it is?
I didn't know.
When you're not there,
you're with me.
- Now you're here...
- You could've talked to me on the phone.
What the hell?
Everyone has their own unique DNA.
Getting caught is in my DNA.
Go on, run!
- Sir, you've got it wrong.
- What you're doing is wrong.
Is this some brothel?
- What did you say?
- Raghu.
Leena, I'm so sorry.
Because of me...
One minute.
What was that word you used?
Don't you dare!
Sorry, sorry.
Must I teach you manners?
- How dare you talk like that!
- Raghu, please.
Leena, I'm just scaring him.
Sorry.
What did you say? Motherf***!
- Go on, say it again!
- No, Raghu, stop.
He shouldn't talk like that.
He didn't give me an option.
He needs a beating.
Raghu, he's a cop.
You can't hit him.
Go. There'll be trouble here.
- Raghu's just scaring him.
- That's not what he's doing.
There'll be big trouble here. Go!
I have to hit him.
He assaulted me.
- I'm done.
- He assaulted me.
- He hit me.
- Check if he's hurt.
Leena!
- This isn't a minor offence.
- I'm so grateful to you.
See the rich doctor's boy!
Got bail in no time.
If he was a poor man like me
he'd be rotting in jail
for attempted murder.
Who's the girl?
Was she punished too?
The doctor's son did it
with Sethji's daughter.
- Went the whole way?
- The whole way?
I can't believe the girl would do
such a thing.
She must have.
Why else would the doctor's son
take her to those ruins?
Sister, depraved behavior.
How can I talk about it?
But what did he do?
What every man wants
to do with a woman.
Goyal's daughter was vomiting
the other day.
- What!
- Yes.
- You sure?
- True or false, find out for yourself.
Goyal's daughter...
Your brother was thrown in jail.
He did a bad thing to that girl.
Heard the gossip that's
spreading in Udaipur?
You can't stop wagging tongues.
- But we know our daughter.
- No, we don't.
Don't go by her innocent face.
She must've done what they say.
- Here?
- Yes, come on.
- What's going on?
- Leena, I'm very serious about you.
I'll never leave you
as long as I live.
I'll take care of you.
I'm very serious about you.
No matter what people may say.
You're talking again?
Your mother is here.
Let's elope.
Get out of here!
- Sorry.
- Go!
Who the hell is this boy?
Hey, boy! You're going to fall.
Hey, you!
- Is Leena upstairs?
- I don't know.
You're going to fall.
Hey, that's him.
The doctor's son.
Someone stop him!
Sorry, Leena.
Bring him here.
Who is he? Stop.
He's the doctor's son.
Leena?
So it's settled?
How many times must I tell you, Sushil?
Take Leena to Delhi right away.
If she stays here,
she'll invite more shame on us.
Her parents decided to send her
to Delhi
so they'd be rid of me.
I was studying medicine
to be a doctor one day.
Like my father.
Father, I've been thinking.
I want to leave medical college.
And you did?
Gave up a career in medicine?
And then?
Look straight ahead.
Don't worry, brother.
Sit down!
Yes, it's you
No, it's you
You're the silence in me
Whether you say it
Or you don't say it
You'll always be mine
Steal me from my path
and take me along
The place where your shadow falls
make some space for me there
I'll meet you wherever you say
I'll abide by you.
I'll always be yours
Belonging only to you. Only you
If there's a you,
there's a me
My need for you
will never fade
Whether you say it
Or you don't say it
You'll always belong to me
Zoe!
Veer, please. Just give me
some time, OK?
Please go away.
What's wrong?
Just ignore me, OK? Let me be.
Veer please, don't look at me.
Go away!
Did I..?
I've had it.
I didn't think this could happen.
So perfect.
I was terrified this would
happen one day.
I made so many plans, had so
many goals so I would
save myself from this.
Because this is what
the real Zoe wants.
To let myself go! F***!
To let myself go.
This is what I want now, Veer.
I'm trapped.
Hey, Zoe.
The moment you feel
I'm in your way...
What's wrong with you?
As if you could be in my way.
But I could be now
because we're close.
You wouldn't care if a stranger
came in your way.
Only those close to you can hurt.
So, the moment you think
I'm in your way, I'll...
- That was scary.
- Get used to it.
- We aren't under-utilizing?
- Optimizing!
Congratulations!
Onyx. You've got the job!
Barnali called.
Start packing.
You have to go to Dubai asap.
It's great for my ego.
Especially after the Mehta Group
rejected me.
But I'm saying no.
- What?
- I've thought it over.
It's not the right time for me
to relocate.
I'll wait for better options.
Better options?
You really thought it through?
What better options?
I don't know, ma. Let's see.
Roaming about with that boy
on his bike is a better option?
What's he gotta do with it?
You mean he hasn't?
What are you saying, ma?
Who do you think I am?
I know you inside out, Zoe.
You know what I'm saying.
Ma, just chill. OK?
Don't say "chill" to me!
I hate this word.
If I hadn't given up my career to marry,
and refused to "chill"
I would not be kneading bread
every day.
Must you keep repeating that?
I say it because
that's my life now, Zoe.
I have to swallow my own ego,
every day.
I must wait till your father sends
money to pay the gardener.
Not the gardener again!
Not that again! Don't you think
I know?
Seher knew too,
but what did she do?
You're changing too.
Don't you think I can see it?
What can you see?
Well? What can you see?
Everyone goes through this phase.
You're not alone.
You're thinking the air is pink,
the sky is purple.
I felt that too
and so did your sister.
Now it's your turn.
You're making a mistake that you'll
regret forever.
You know what, ma?
I've had enough.
I'm calling him.
I'm going to him.
Drop that bag down, Zoe.
Behave!
No, ma. I can't take it anymore.
I've had it up to here.
- I need a break.
- Come back here.
- What are you doing?
- I can't take it anymore.
I'll call you later.
Wow! You're both on the fast track.
It's not that.
It's only for a short time.
Hey! It is that.
You're moving in with your bags
and baggage.
Yes, I'm moving in with him. So?
So nothing! Enjoy!
My dad would've killed me if
I had done this.
What's up?
Everything's happening so fast.
I'm sure I'll feel better once
I've spoken to Raj.
He'll talk about romance
and I'll feel better.
- I'll let Mr Raj know.
- Is he in his office?
Ma'am, he's busy.
- Ma'am, please.
- Don't worry.
One second.
Zoe?
This is a sign.
One second.
You can't imagine how excited
I am to see you here.
It's just what I've been looking for.
Sorry, I'm Zoe.
You don't know me,
but I know everything about you.
Really?
The balcony, the scooter,
the roof terrace meetings.
The guard who caught you
at the ruins.
The romantic movie - everything.
I think there's some...Raj?
Zoe. Farhana.
Farhana - Zoe.
Hi, Zoe.
I'm sorry.
Confusion.
I'm so sorry.
You thought I was someone else.
Just forget it, please.
I'm sorry.
Zoe!
Listen, it's none of my business.
- I shouldn't have barged in like that.
- Sorry.
Why?
Why apologize?
I spoilt your fairytale.
I killed your Santa Claus.
I didn't want to disappoint you.
You drove me crazy.
Telling me your sweet romantic story.
You made me believe
love was possible.
And you are with
someone else?
How?
Life, Zoe.
Things happens in life.
What do you mean?
Did Leena die?
You left home for her.
You left medical college.
You abandoned your career
your city, everything.
What went wrong?
I started working at a restaurant
as a floor manager.
To earn some money.
I worked 16 hours a day,
slept for 4.
Then I'd see Leena for 2 hours.
The last ten minutes
just before sleeping
was my time.
That's when I'd think of Leena.
Why are you telling me all this?
What happened?
One day...
Leena came to the restaurant
to see me.
Raghuvendra, your girlfriend is here.
You came by bus?
Madam, this way.
Another girl?
- Who was she?
- Who was I?
Don't you have to meet
your girlfriend?
No. Her hostel closes at nine.
Do you miss her?
A lot.
You know I miss my boyfriend
a lot too.
Where is he?
The one thing you thought
you'd never do
one day you've done it.
Just like that.
Then?
Then there was another girl.
Then another.
And another.
Why?
Hard to explain now.
Back then I never met any girls.
In Udaipur there was only Leena.
And I was crazy about her.
I was totally committed to her,
I promised her everything.
Then I came here and discovered
a different world.
I had so many options.
Then I figured I was too rash
to have committed myself to her.
I made a mistake.
Come.
- Did you tell Leena?
- Of course not.
I said nothing.
I kept the farce going, spoke the
same romantic dialogue.
I started giving her flowers.
Candle-lit dinners.
Then one day she caught me
with a girl.
Thank you, sir!
Come back soon.
Leena, I don't know what you saw.
But it's not how it looks.
Raghu.
You're the person
who left everything behind and ran
onto the train.
You gave up your whole world
for me.
Do you think I could ever
doubt you?
Is that possible?
I know you.
You're Raghu.
You belong more to me
than to yourself.
That day I decided
I would leave Leena.
I couldn't be with her anymore.
I used to feel guilty around her.
I started avoiding her;
making excuses not to see her.
I created situations in the hope
she'd leave me.
You haven't seen me
in a whole month.
Can't you get two hours off?
It's a new job, Leena.
You can't even call me?
- Is Raghuvendra there?
- No.
- When will he be back?
- Don't know.
I'll tell him to call you
when he's back.
My parents were here, you know?
They were asking about you.
They know about us.
They wanted to meet you.
But you weren't taking my calls.
They want me to move to Mumbai
to study.
Can you imagine
the pressure on me?
Stop stressing, Leena.
I feel terrible. Just stop seeing me.
One day I came to work and she was
already there.
She looked different.
You know what?
Don't tell me anything more.
What's it to me?
Why have I got so involved?
It's your life.
And who are you to me?
No. Really.
You're here?
Do you get attracted to girls?
Yeah.
Don't you get attracted to boys?
I feel like drinking petrol too!
- What's the issue?
- You...
And me.
We'll sort it out.
First let's sort my mom out!
- That's no big deal.
- What?
She's asked you to dinner.
She knows about us.
Dad will be in town too.
F***!
You can say no.
I haven't said we'd come.
- Why refuse?
- It's making you tense.
- And it's not worth it.
- Of course I'm tense.
My clothes are at my mom's.
I'll have to get dressed there.
- Zoe, do you wanna go?
- Don't you?
What shall I wear? Formal?
Don't irritate me.
What shall I wear?
Let me see.
My baby.
Always beautiful.
I know it's an important day
for you.
And I'm sorry.
I kept nagging you
to have a career.
I ended up putting you off it.
You're my daughter after all.
As if I ever listened.
So what will be will be.
Go, enjoy yourself.
If I hadn't given up my career to marry,
and refused to "chill"
I would not be kneading bread
every day.
One mistake.
And your entire life slips
through your fingers.
You can't rewind it.
How beautiful everything seems
at the beginning. Such fun.
Give me an example of a couple
having as much fun later.
Money is very important, child.
Never compromise on your ability
to earn.
Don't be a fool.
You can't depend on anyone,
only yourself.
Shall we?
I've got the Onyx job.
The company was second on my list
after Mehta industries.
But I deleted their email.
I didn't tell anyone.
Not even you.
- If you didn't want the job...
- Can't you hear me?
Of course I wanted it.
I was waiting for it
so desperately.
My career is everything to me.
I am killing my career. Hiding my
ambition from everyone including myself.
Already.
Let me see.
This is the first time my son
is introducing us to a girl.
All for you.
To be with you.
How can I go to Dubai?
The air is pink, the sky is purple.
We're having such fun.
Zoe, let's talk later.
Why? Why talk later?
Veer, we're making a mistake.
S***! F***!
Hello, auntie.
I'm really sorry.
Something's happened
and I got hyper.
It's OK, child. It's fine.
Now you're making a mistake
that you'll regret forever.
Hello. Zoe.
Satyarth. "Sat," if you like.
My parents were here, you know?
Can you imagine
the pressure on me?
One day when I came home
after an official two-month trip...
You know I'm a bit tense.
I'm really sorry.
Veer, let me just say it,
it's a compromise.
I'm compromising.
Zoe, you're overreacting.
Of course I'm overreacting.
The one thing you thought
you'd never do
one day you've done it.
Just like that.
I wanted so much
to impress you both.
I've messed it up.
Stop, stop.
Zoe, whatever it is, we'll sort it out.
Remember?
No. It cannot be sorted, Veer.
It's done.
What's done, Zoe?
Nothing's happened. Just relax.
It's fine.
It's over.
You've started to come in my way.
I'm moving to Mumbai.
- When?
- Next week.
I'll drop you to the station.
So difficult to decide
Do I tell you what I feel
or stay silent?
Coming close may drive you away
I come with my wounds
and sufferings
And undo the things
I dream of doing
Instead of coming closer to you,
what did I find?
These distances
Hello, driver.
They say all your feelings
must be reserved
for only one woman.
That's impossible for me!
My eyes keep roving.
I see one woman then another.
My bull can mate with ten cows.
I have a goat.
I've never heard it say:
"Sorry! I'm in a committed relationship."
In fact, if it sees another goat,
it bleats, "me, me."
And me? If I talked like that
I'd be labelled a sinner.
Is this fair?
Is this the world you've created?
You're made to feel guilty 25 times
in 24 hours.
Why should I feel guilty?
It's just lust.
Brothers, I bought this lust
at the general store.
It's a gift from God.
Everyone lusts.
You do, I do.
And my bull does.
God has given us all
the same private parts, right?
But my bull roams about stark naked
while I must stay all covered. Why?
Objection!
Justice Chaudhary says,
"Objection, milord!"
If my bull can roam about naked
why should I hide my private parts?
Hey, you!
This is your love story
Listen carefully
You saw her,
she saw you
Fell head over heels
Her eyes pierced your heart
Love's in the air.
Heart's in 4th gear
You'll never leave her.
You promised
Stress will bring you closer
Wow! Two bodies, one soul
You're where she is
Like a trailing shadow,
she's on top, you're below
You'll fight, you'll commit
See that trap?
Now you've fallen into it
Our rituals, our traps
O Lord!
Social tyrants,
fake humans
O Lord!
Our guilt, our shame
You're in heaven,
the world's a doghouse
O Lord!
These sham show-offs
This phony talk.
I'll kick you on the butt
If I was a donkey,
I'd sleep where I please
No one scolds my bull,
he roams about stark naked
Shackled we are.
Decked in clothes
Wake up. Run!
Get yourself another lover
Why are you stuck
on monogamy?
Why flounder in
romantic confusion?
Why get stuck in
inorganic equations?
They bind us with their rituals
Some will break down
They trap me and make me
what I'm not
They've cheated me, milord
- So early?
- Yeah. Hi!
She's not here yet.
Can I leave this here?
She'll pick it up later.
Going somewhere?
I'm not coming back.
Actually, I want to close my account.
- I'll pay at the counter...
- What's wrong?
- What did she do?
- Forget it.
Tell me.
No point getting into all that.
I think I'm already in it.
So what did she do?
No, drop it.
She must follow her heart.
I can't believe it!
Is she that silly?
Making a mountain of a molehill.
Let me talk to her.
Listen, please don't.
Of course I will.
Then she'll come back to me.
Yeah.
Because you told her to.
Then she won't get the chance
to come back because she wants to.
She's right.
Hello.
"If you love someone, set them free."
That's advice for other people.
Not something you do.
The world is not perfect.
- Who says!
- "Who says?" I say!
I've been around 20 years
longer than you.
I can guarantee this world
is far from perfect.
Thanks, man.
I know you're sincere.
But there are some lessons
I want to learn for myself.
That's cool, right?
What if you lose her?
If she doesn't come back?
You don't have to play
the brave guy, sonny.
Everything can go downhill.
I know.
You think I don't know that?
But I don't want her back if I'm
going to lose her again.
There are so many couples
who live together
but aren't together.
I couldn't bear that.
I get you.
Don't push her.
It'll be a mess.
Congratulations, ma.
As you can see,
no bike came to pick me up.
I'm not your enemy, child.
The '80s are over. Or you could've
been a hit movie dialogue writer.
- You missed your chance.
- Don't miss yours.
- Zoe Chauhan.
- They're waiting for you, ma'am.
I thought I'd killed my chances last time.
And you'd never call me back.
You were shameless,
you were cocky
and generally inappropriate.
Since we value qualities like that
we want you to organize an event
we think you're bound to mess up.
All the best!
Don't wait for me.
I'm calling from the Mehta Group
Head office.
Yes, the same!
Barnali is calling all the vendors here.
The backdrop is set.
The chairs are being set up.
In two hours, the AV system arrives.
You've gone through the checklist twice.
Chill!
Did you ever think we'd get
a Mehta Group event?
- So? Are you ready to fail?
- Fully, sir!
I must say your dress code
is rather unexpected.
I'll check everything one last time,
then I'll get changed.
- Hurry up!
- Shut up!
We'll need this much space.
It's fine if the client wants
an open-air event
but in an open mall
or a mill compound?
Is this OK?
Yeah. Thanks.
The client hasn't specified anything.
They're fine with anything.
So we'll ask them.
Pragati Maidan or Cyber City?
As far as the décor
of the event is concerned
I'm thinking we should go
with earthy tones.
Yeah, maybe more browns
and greens.
That'll match the theme of
the event as well as your branding.
I hope everything's checked
because once the event starts to roll
it must roll from one end to another,
no matter what.
- Maybe this one...
- No, this.
Make sure all the food is being served.
Zoe Chauhan, Mr Mehta wanted
to meet you.
- Hi, sir!
- I see.
- Why isn't she working full-time for us?
- You're right, sir. Why not?
- Keep this one close.
- Zoe!
- Wasn't that Harshvardhan Mehta?
- Yeah.
- What did he say?
- One second, ma.
Happy?
Are you happy?
Maybe.
Maybe?
You don't know if you're happy?
Everything's going so well.
Your career is taking off.
So I must be happy.
I don't know.
One second.
Look who's here.
- How are you?
- Super-fantastic.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
That's my new line.
Whenever anyone asks me,
that's what I say.
Mom asked me if I was happy.
I thought, "s***."
I don't even know.
I can't feel anything these days.
I've become someone else.
I've invented a new detox drink.
Wanna try it?
How did you do it?
You own four restaurants
and this café too.
You started from scratch.
I'm finding it so tough.
I'm becoming a robot.
So how did you manage it?
As if I did.
When my boyfriend and your
girlfriend are far away
we make do with one another.
Besides Tuteja has us working
like dogs.
So we deserve some fun.
Life, yeah?
I'm learning.
Don't learn too much.
It's not like you bought lust
from a general store.
What you felt came naturally.
God's gift.
I'm not going to spin you some yarn
to justify what I've done.
What I did is wrong.
And that's it.
What's right, what's wrong?
These rules are made by society.
They keep changing.
Some years ago gay relationships
were unacceptable, now they're accepted.
So you did what was natural
for you.
All this love and passion
for one person.
To love one person for a whole lifetime,
that's not natural.
All this romantic bull****
is just fed to us.
So we stay in line.
A kinda mental jail.
Slow down, slow down, kid!
You're taking it too far.
Correct.
Balancing life and a career
is hard
which is really not happening.
My personal life is zero.
How have you managed such
a colorful personal life?
Remember? Getting caught
is in my DNA.
Again?
You scum!
What were you thinking?
Is this a brothel?
Come downstairs now!
Leave this door open!
Let everyone see your nakedness.
Come down!
Take a good look at them!
And you, Raghuvinder!
Day and night you've bored me
with stories of your girlfriend.
And this is what you're up to?
I'm talking to you!
Have you no shame?
- I'm standing right here.
- What?
You don't need to shout.
How dare you talk to me
like that?
That's it, get out! Out!
Hey, you! Don't be so jealous.
Jealous? Jealous?
- Turning green!
- I know what "jealous" means.
That's it, you get out too. Out!
Sweetu, the owner of Zenith
offered me 10,000 rupees a month.
I'm gonna ask for 15,000.
Come with me,
we'll talk to him together.
He's opening a new section.
He'll need another manager.
Stealing staff from under my nose!
Who wants higher wages?
Come with us.
Get this fella out of here.
You dog, you lowlife.
Out! Throw him out now.
Are you deaf?
If you don't pay me 25,000,
I'm not coming back.
Did you really say all that?
He came back to me a month later
with an offer of 25,000.
- So you went back?
- No.
Because another restaurant
offered me even more.
But the point is when I came to Delhi,
I changed.
I became street-smart.
I became familiar
with market rates.
I worked in many restaurants,
my wages kept rising.
A few years later an investor suggested
I open my own place.
Rag..vinder?
Raj. Just call me Raj.
And you went from girl to girl
with no girlfriend to stop you.
Then I opened this café.
And another girl...
I dislike her habits.
She keeps changing her mind.
She said, "Let's take a bus."
When we got on the bus, she said,
"It's too crowded." How odd!
O Jesus!
- Whoa!
- Yeah.
So? Can I follow you?
- I'm not on Social Media.
- Didn't you work on their app?
Yes. That's why.
Funny boy.
If your work's done,
shall we grab a beer?
That's the only way
I can follow you.
- You're wasting your time.
- Why?
I'm focusing on my career.
- On Mummy's say so?
- No, my ex.
Why bother about your ex?
But I still do. Yeah.
Take me on the rebound.
You're cute.
- But I can't do it.
- Leave that to me.
OK. Let's try.
For real?
See?
This is possible without you.
I mean it's possible without a girl.
Sorry.
OK, bye.
Beer? We can still grab one.
Let's go!
Thank you!
You get so many job offers.
So what's the problem?
I don't want those kind of jobs.
I don't know what I want.
Do you like me?
- Do you like me?
- Honestly...
- Good, we're safe.
- Cheers!
Plastic is anti-nature.
Plastic is inorganic.
Plastic is a crime committed
by everyone.
Know what the punishment is?
Plastic!
Nothing, right?
We are doing so well.
Another date is guaranteed.
You know China makes plastic rice.
We could go all the way
after a few dates.
After that, it's the usual.
Nothing.
Plastic was born from
man's greed for money.
Money, money, money.
Do you know what bank notes
are made of?
So finally you're back, baby.
You say "baby" like you're
gonna have one.
For that we'd need
to do something first, Zoe!
Another round.
Take it. I haven't touched it.
- Where are we going?
- Home.
No, I said "my home."
Does it matter whose home, baby?
Home is home.
You've got it wrong.
Turn the car around.
What you doing? I told you
I was feeling dizzy.
Enough, just stop.
You're such a sweet cute little baby.
- You don't get it, do you?
- Meaning?
I've been flattering you
for months.
I've taken you to one expensive joint
after another. What for?
Look. I'm feeling sick.
I'm going to throw up.
My head's spinning.
You should get an Oscar, by God!
Please. Just drop me home now.
We'll talk tomorrow.
You're hot but not that hot.
Don't act so pricey.
Tantrums girls make
should match their looks.
Please, please, drop me home.
This car's heading to my place.
That's it. The rest is your call.
F***!
Next time I'll pay a whore
10 grand instead.
She'll be better value.
I'm really sorry, Veer.
- I shouldn't have called you.
- It's fine.
Were you headed this way?
Zoe, stand.
Look at me, Zoe.
Look at me.
I yearn for a place of peace
It's something I've often wished
But I have never found peace
My heart is too reasonable
Why do I not get
to the place I yearn for?
Where did I lose myself?
What has come over me?
O Companion,
what did you gain
by being apart from me?
I have lost myself
Nor could I find you
O Companion,
what did you gain
by being apart from me?
Fine?
Oh, Zoe!
I miss you every day,
every moment.
But this is a moment
of weakness.
Hush!
You haven't come back to me.
You're just feeling vulnerable.
Just hold me.
- This is a compromise, Zoe.
- Will you be quiet?
I hate it.
You were right.
We were under-utilizing
our relationship.
You were right.
Only those close to you
can hurt.
But what's the point?
We still left each other, right?
Now you're here.
And I'm here.
It's possible for us
to melt into this moment.
And stay there. Let time
pass us by.
Bring each other some relief.
Do you have to keep talking
about inner truth?
And ruining the moment again.
But you'll go away again, Zoe.
You're not fully with me.
Not that again!
What's your problem?
Yes, I have a problem.
I didn't need you for sex.
And if I wanted to compromise
in a relationship like my parents,
I could have that with anyone.
But not with you.
I want all of you, Zoe.
The inner Zoe, the outer Zoe;
career Zoe, family Zoe. Full!
Not the one who has to hide
behind alcohol to see me.
You'll always be as stupid.
I can't help it, Zoe.
I try very hard
but I can't change.
Maybe everyone else is right,
and I'm the stupid idiot who's wrong
to believe there's more in this world
than 2+2=4.
It's possible...
to be happy with someone.
An ideal relationship is possible.
But if I'm right, Zoe
then this is the only chance
for us.
You and me.
I'm not wasting that chance.
Be with me fully
or don't be with me at all.
Then go! Be alone.
The world's problems
are not meant to be solved.
You'll discover the
ultimate truth someday.
And thank you for bringing me home.
I hope in future
I'm never that weak
to be forced to see you.
More than 2+2=4.
That's what Majnu and Romeo wanted.
And Veer too.
That's not how things work
in this world.
There is no magic.
Who knows.
Maybe he'll find magic.
Did you meet again?
Next morning.
Driver, where are you?
I'm waiting outside.
Hey, Zoe.
I wanted to thank you.
When you broke up with me
I felt terrible.
But it taught me something.
You broke up with me because
you wanted a career.
So I thought what about
my career?
I was always going on about Zoe, Zoe.
Never gave my career a thought.
Even if you're with someone,
there's more to life.
Thanks to you I started
looking around for work.
And finally found the job
I really want to do.
- In an American company?
- In the Himalayas.
It's a multi-purpose project,
water harnessing.
A two-year project.
I'm moving there. So...
So?
It's not as though
I don't want to see you.
We may not get
another chance.
So take a good look.
There's you
And only you
Every moment is spent
in thought of you
Why did you walk
the long road with me?
You were unaware
You are in my every moment,
you walk on my every path
Why did you take me so far?
I would never have made
promises to you
Or would I have forgotten them
In my search on every road
I see you there
Your presence makes
your absence feel sharper
There's you
And only you
You can make me cry with laughter
By now I know you well
If you're not by my side,
then free my thoughts of you
If you must leave me
let me go
Why can't I get you off my mind?
Welcome.
A lonely life is no life
It's dying without dying
This life is no life
if it's filled with tears
Your presence makes
your absence feel sharper
Sorry.
Sorry, sir.
Oh! The events girl? Chauhan, Zoe!
- Yes, sir.
- Sorry to barge in, Zoe.
No, sir! This is your office.
It's Saturday night.
Why isn't your boyfriend
taking you out?
Don't tell me you don't have
a boyfriend.
Sir, work is my boyfriend.
That's a line for your clients.
Sometimes we speak the truth
to clients.
You're too young to think like that.
Tell me why have you made your work
your boyfriend?
Because it's always there
for me.
- It doesn't waste my time.
- Very good.
And it pays the bills.
It guides me, it's completely safe.
So whenever I feel lonely,
I go and hug him.
And he makes me feel better.
What?
Harshvardhan Mehta
dropped by last night.
Really?
He was at my office the other day.
But why did he come here?
Sit!
What's going on?
Mr Harshvardhan Mehta
wants you to marry his grandson,
Rishabh Mehta.
He said you've met.
And you really get on.
These rich business families
believe in marrying young.
Anyway he came here.
He said everyone in his family
like you very much.
So now it's OK to give up
my career?
So I no longer need
to be independent?
Now I can forget what you've
drummed into me all my life?
Zoe, your life and mine
are not alike.
No rich Mehta ever proposed
to me.
Then I'll tell Rishabh to marry you
instead of marrying me.
Besides, my mother is prettier
than I am. Right?
Bravo, Mummy!
I can only tell you and your sister
what I believe is right.
Maybe I'm not always right.
Sometimes I offload my insecurities
on you.
But I try.
I try.
Don't worry, cutie pie.
I'm a big girl now.
I guess we end up
parenting our parents.
It's damn confusing.
You spend your life believing
a certain truth
then suddenly, whoop - all changes!
Practical needs never go away.
You'll always need money.
Love with your heart,
but marry with your head.
Marriages that last
are practical ones.
Just look around.
You know what? Eff this world!
Hi, Zoe.
This world will always be complicated.
It'll keep creating new situations
to drive me crazy.
Whichever road I take,
I'll see a "No Entry" sign.
So I give a...
So, how's life?
Just tell me a story.
A romantic, Leena story.
Transport me to a distant place.
At least for a while.
OK.
So...
Four years after Leena left
I was in a hotel.
A girl was with me.
Hello! I don't want to hear
about your escapades.
You want to hear about Leena, no?
The romantic parts.
This part is the most romantic.
Leena...
Leena?
Four years later?
Out of the blue?
Out of the blue.
Let's watch the match, Leena.
I ignored it three times.
Fed up of you calling me "Leena!"
Go to her.
There was no reason for it.
It wasn't as though I was alone.
I spent almost every night
with a girl.
Weren't you in touch with Leena?
All I knew was that
she was in Mumbai.
Stay longer.
No, my friend. Sorry, guys,
gotta go.
Personal stuff.
Never understood
Leena's effect on me.
What was so special about her?
I spent time with so many girls.
But Leena had something
that belonged to me.
I kept making excuses to escape,
from girls too.
I'd say I had personal stuff
to sort out and go.
But the last ten minutes
before I'd fall asleep
was my time.
I spent that time
thinking about Leena.
Personal stuff!
Isn't this story romantic?
Didn't you try and reach out to her?
A friend always pops up
in a story like this.
- And this one came from America.
- Welcome home!
We both got sozzled,
and like typical Indians, we started
fighting over the bill.
The story gets even more romantic.
Let me treat you.
Rathore knew Leena's whereabouts.
Some friends were in touch with her.
She was running a café in Mumbai.
Go on! Go to her.
I can't show her my face.
I behaved so badly.
I was so cruel to her.
You're sitting here with her photo,
dying to see her again.
So die! You deserve to.
You did wrong.
But what did she do wrong?
Why should she suffer?
If you behaved badly, you should
make up to her.
Spend your life looking after her.
Just like you wanted to.
It's been 5 years, 3 months, Rathore.
Life is much longer than that.
You and Leena were made
for each other.
We knew that since school.
Raghu and Leena - the Romeo
and Juliet of Udaipur.
Go, Raghu, go!
- Did you go?
- That very moment.
Mumbai, first flight.
Leena? Was she there?
Yes.
She was.
She was sitting inside.
The same... Leena.
The man I am
and the man I wanted to be
were two separate people.
They could never be one.
I didn't lose Leena that day.
But that day
I lost
the person I once was.
Love is not a promise
Love is not a ritual
My heart is not mistaken
It's you I want
That rare path
that leads to a place of dreams
In that place called love
It's you I want to find
Wherever you go
You'll find me there
I want nothing more than you
Nothing less than you
Without you
There is no me
Now I look for myself
in others.
I'm constantly looking
in everyone I meet.
In you.
Who are you to me, really?
What difference does it make
how your story turns out?
Why would I care
that you do not lose
what I have lost?
Even if you find him,
I know I'll never have
my Leena.
Do better than me, kid.
Please.
Eyes well with tears
make the path ahead hazy
The desires of my heart
are no longer within my reach
He's gone.
He left six months ago.
Perhaps I will find
who I once was
Perhaps I will know
this path is not for me
Instead of being close to you,
what did I find?
These distances
You've come.
With all the old problems.
Nothing's changed.
I'll never strike a balance
between my career and you.
I don't know what balance is.
But how can I stay apart
from you?
Whether it's natural for two people
to always stay together or not
I don't know.
I ask myself
am I making a mistake?
Zoe,
is there anyone else in this world
with whom you'd rather make
this mistake?
No, Veer.
But in the beginning
everything's wonderful.
The start is so much fun.
But what I feel for you right now
will it change?
What if it ends?
It will.
Everything ends one day.
Then?
One day your life will end too.
The world will end someday.
But that day is not today.
Today I want to make this mistake.
I want to climb the mountain top
and jump off it.
Zoe, will you jump with me?
Let's go.
OK.
Yeah.
Now we're on.
Yes, I'm wrong
My words are wrong
The world was created
with a mistake
No one is completely right
Let me warn you
Do as your heart pleases today
The stage is set.
Do it with a twist
Yes, I'm wrong
You be wrong too
Let's be wrong together
Cowards are never right
Many miss the boat
The sky tears apart
The world turns its back
But the stage is set.
Do it with a twist
My unique character,
your unique traits
We'll break, scatter,
falter and steady ourselves
Don't apply reason
to the ways of the heart
If we go by our heads
we'll stumble
Do as your heart pleases today
The stage is set.
Do it with a twist